<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Nexmeer</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nexmeer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.152.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:26:26 +0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction To Hugo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:26:26 +0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hugo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hugo is a static site generator based on Go. It is known for its blazing speed and flexibility, allowing it to render sites within a second or less. It has an advanced templating system that makes it incredibly powerful for building modern websites. Hugo comes with its own server having hot reload functionality, so you can see the site changes instantly in your browser.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;installing-hugo&#34;&gt;Installing Hugo&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, if you already have an older version of Hugo installed, you need to remove it to avoid version conflicts:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Git &amp; Github</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/git-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:50:41 +0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/git-github/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Imagine you are working on a large-scale project where you are testing different approaches to a problem. You solve the problem but you want to further improve it. You power off your system and again work on the project another day. You find that the problem can&amp;rsquo;t be solved any other way and the only solution to that problem is the one you implemented previously. But there is no way to revert it back. &lt;strong&gt;This is where Git comes in.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started With Linux</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:40:43 +0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/linux/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently started using Linux and found it to be an amazing and powerful system. If you are the kind of person who likes to get most things done from the keyboard without touching the mouse, you will find Linux to be the perfect system for you. In this article, I will guide you through Linux so that you will be comfortable starting to use it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;-what-is-linux&#34;&gt;🐧 What is Linux?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Linux is an &lt;strong&gt;open-source operating system&lt;/strong&gt;, meaning it is software that manages the hardware of a computer. It is freely available for anyone to use and modify. Linux is built around the &lt;strong&gt;Linux kernel&lt;/strong&gt;, which is responsible for managing memory and system resources. Linux comes in different versions called &lt;strong&gt;distributions (distros)&lt;/strong&gt;, such as &lt;strong&gt;Fedora, Debian, and Ubuntu&lt;/strong&gt;. Each distribution has its own interface and features, but the underlying architecture is the same.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:02:32 +0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is my first post using Hugo and PaperMod.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
